Hello friends, welcome to my channel. Friends,
today in this video we are going to talk about a
hidden Rustam plan which has become
quieter than the big health insurance plans in the market,
but if I talk about its features, then
you will say that the product really has
potential. Yes friends, I am talking about
Tata AKK Medicare Premium Plan.
Friends, in this plan company Advance Plans
Plan, the company has tried to provide such features
which a customer wants to find in a good health
insurance plan. So let's move ahead
and do things one by one.
So my name is Abhishek Goyal and welcome to my
channel investor. Friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
please subscribe so that all of you keep
getting such better information. So let's move ahead
and understand the details of this product.
Friends, we have divided this product
into categories. First we will talk about the
general features, after that we will talk about the
unique features, then along with
optional benefits and premium and other details.
So first of all let's talk about the general features.
In the general features, the first thing we talk about is
minimum entries.  Friends, in this
product, the
maximum age limit is 65 years. Next,
friends, room rent and this charge, friends,
the company has not given any limitations in this. You are being provided up to six months tax. Next is pre-hospital and post-hospital expenses, that is, expenses before admission to the hospital and expenses after withdrawal. So, if your policy is below Rs 50 lakh, then the company is giving you 60 days
free hospitalization and
90 days post-hospitalization. If
your policy is above Rs 50 lakh, then the
company is providing you up to 100 days post-
hospitalization expenses.
Next is no-claim bonus. Friends, if you do
not take any claim in your policy, then
as soon as you renew the policy, the
company increases your insurance by 50%.
Again, if you do not take a claim in the next year, then the
company again increases your insurance by 50%,
which covers 100% of your maximum base
policy expenses. And if these are increased
in the future  If it happens then the company
reduces your no claim bonus by 50% in its subsequent year.
Next is restore benefit friends, in this case
if you have any claim due to which
your base submission and your no claim
bonus gets lost then the company
gives you restore benefit.
Friends, there is a catch in this, the company says that you will
get restore benefit only after 45 days for this disease, but if it is a different
disease then you get immediate restore
benefit.
Next is organ donor friends, many times it happens
that any organ of our body fails due to
which a donor
donates an organ to us, then whatever
expenses the organ donor has in the hospital, that
too the company is providing you with the same, apart from
your base care
treatment friends, there are many treatments in
which consultation is not required in today's date,
like kidney stone cataract, in
which you get treatment in two to two hours
and you are taken out, so
in this case also the company provides you up to
power  Next is
home care and domicile treatment, that is,
some such diseases in which hospitalization
is required relief, but you are
taking that treatment from home, then whatever expenses are
incurred, the company is providing you the benefit and tax.
Next is AYUSH
benefit, that is, Ayurveda, Yoga, Unani,
Jinda, Homeopathic. If apart from allopathy treatment,
if you want to get any of these treatments,
if you are taking any treatment related to all these in any recognized institute or government hospital, then the
company is also providing you the cost
and tax for that.
Next is road ambulance, friends, this is
slab wise, if you have a policy below 50 lakhs,
then you get a tax of ₹5000.
Next is ambulance, in this friends,
you are being given ₹500. If you are
taking emergency and ambulance in a network hospital, then there is
no limitation given in it. So, in this way,
friends, we have covered the common features, now let's talk about the
unique feature due to which this
product becomes different from other products.
First of all, let's talk about HI and diagnostic
test coverage.  OPD basis means that
many times it happens that
some symptoms of some serious disease are seen in our body
due to which the doctor does brain imaging, CT
scan, MRI or PACS consensus things
but no disease has been detected in our body
but the
company also gives you a claim for the expenses behind it,
please friends, your slice is if you have a
policy below 50 lakhs then you are
getting coverage up to 25000.
Next is global coverage friends,
in this product you are getting global coverage,
yes friends, if you have to go
out of India for treatment of any critical illness then the
company gives claim for that also, the
only condition is that the disease has been
diagnosed in India only,
in this also friends the company is providing you by submitting,
next is free
checkup from D the one of D policy, that is, if you
take such an N policy then the company
gives you free help checkup for ₹10000 which
you can get done in any national pathology center,
provide the bill and report to the company, the company gives you your money.
Next is OPD  Expense Tax
Friends, in this product, as soon as your 2 years are
completed, the company is giving you OPD expenses up to ₹5000, that is,
if
you have normal medicines and doctor
expenses for any minor cold, cough, the company is providing you a tax of ₹5000.
Next is Dental
OPD Tax, in this also friends, after
continuous air of coverage, the company
provides you a tax of ₹10000 up to Dental OPD Expense, in which you can avail root
canal, tooth filling or teeth extraction.
Next is Prolong
Hospital Benefit, friends, if you get
admitted to the hospital due to any disease or injury, then the company
gives you a separate benefit of One Day Off Shoot, that is, if you have a policy of 10 lakhs, then the
company gives you a separate benefit of ₹10000.
Next is Compassionate Travel
Expense, friends, this happens many times,
we went out many times where  We have to face hospitalization due to any illness
or injury, in
which none of our family members is relieved,
so keeping this in mind the company has
also given compassionate travel expenses in which it also pays the expenses of your
immediate family member to travel to your location, be it
train ticket or any other ticket.
Vaccination tax is being
provided. Next is daily cash
on the company and insured child. Friends, if
any child in your policy is below 12 years of age
and he is getting admitted in the hospital
due to any reason, then the
company also pays you the expenses of hospital relief.
Next is maternity coverage.
Friends, in this product the company is
also giving you maternity tax after 4 years of waiting.
In this, friends, if you have a
policy below 50 lakhs, then you are being given a tax of 50,000. Whereas in case
of girl child,
you are being provided a tax of 60,000.
Next is first year child
vaccination coverage. In this, friends, the company will give
you vaccination of up to 10,000.  It is providing tax
and in these cases of girl child,
coverage of Rs 15000 is being provided. Next is
hearing aid expense. Friends, if
you are facing any problem in hearing due to which the
doctor is giving you a hearing aid, then
you are going to be provided coverage of up to Rs 10000 in it
or the company will provide you 50% cost of the machine.
If you want to undergo any treatment or
surgery to reduce the cost, then the company will also
provide you the same tax. So friends, in
this way we have shown you unique features. I
hope you liked the information. Now let's talk about
optional tax. Friends, in this product the
company is also providing you accidental death tax.
In this, it is
providing 100% or maximum 50 lakh coverage of your time.
So along with this, friends, the company is
also providing you wellness services in which
along with tele consultation, you are also
providing services like ambulance booking.
Now let's talk about waiting period.
Friends, today as usual, in all the products, the
initial waiting period is 30 days.
Accidental tax on acceptance means
you get tax for any diseases only after 30 days.
Next is 2 years waiting period, that is,
diseases which take time to develop in your body
like kidney stone, hernia,
piles, cataract, all such diseases have a
waiting period of 12 years. Before that, if
you get any claim, then the company does
not give you the claim. Next is 2 years
waiting period for periodic diseases, that is,
before taking the policy, if you have any disease like
BP, sugar or thyroid, then after that,
if any claim comes from this, then the
company does not give you the claim for the next 12 years. That is your graveyard,
after that it becomes applicable. So
friends, in this way we have done the waiting period.
Now let's talk about network hospitals.
Friends, Tata has
more than 7000 network hospitals, so in this case of
cashless, you will find almost all the big hospitals
in the network hospital list, so
you will not face any problem. If
you get treatment in a non-network hospital in emergency,
then you
can take your claim through compensation,
for which you  Get
your clean put up by contacting your agency or directly the company, the
company gives the money, now let's talk about
premium friends, if I
see the premium of 10 lakhs for adult or child, then it comes in T1 category 31335, in
tier 2 category it comes 27367 and
in tier 3 category it comes
23449, in this house if you disclose any of your pre-existing diseases while taking the policy, then
the company charges a separate loading charge for it from
you. Friends, we have reviewed the
product, I hope you
liked the information, if you have any
health insurance, retirement or query,
then you can ask us in the comment box
or you can contact us on the number given below,
we will try to answer you, but if you
liked the video then like
and subscribe to the channel because your every
like motivates us to make such great
videos.